A Guide to the Harry F. Byrd Jr. Papers
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series II: Legislative Files
  - Foreign Relations: Greece (Cyprus), 1974 August 20-November; (3 folders) (Box Box 269)
  - Foreign Relations: Greece - Cyprus, 1974 July-August 1-19, 1975-1976, 1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 270)
  - Foreign Relations: India, 1973-1980 (Box Box 270)
  - Foreign Relations: Iran, 1979, 1980 May-December; (4 folders) (Box Box 270)
  - Foreign Relations: Iran, 1980 January-April, 1981-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 271)
  - Foreign Relations: Israel, 1972-1975 June-December; (3 folders) (Box Box 271)
  - Foreign Relations: Israel, 1975 January-May, 1976-1981; (7 folders) (Box Box 272)
  - Foreign Relations: Israel, 1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 273)
  - Foreign Relations: Israel Trip, 1974 (Box Box 273)
  - Foreign Relations: Japan, 1973-1982 (Box Box 273)
  - Foreign Relations: Korea, 1973-1981; (3 folders) (Box Box 274)
  - Foreign Relations: Laos, 1973-1981 (Box Box 274)
  - Foreign Relations: Marianas Islands, 1975-1978 (Box Box 274)
  - Foreign Relations: Panama, 1973-1974; (4 folders) (Box Box 274)
  - Foreign Relations: Panama, 1975-1976; (8 folders) (Box Box 275)
  - Foreign Relations: Panama, 1977 October 17-December 30; (7 folders) (Box Box 276)
  - Foreign Relations: Panama, 1977 September 15-October 14; (7 folders) (Box Box 277)
  - Foreign Relations: Panama, 1977 August 14-September 14; (7 folders) (Box Box 278)
  - Foreign Relations: Panama, 1977 January-August, 1978 May-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 279)
  - Foreign Relations: Panama, 1978 March 10-April; (8 folders) (Box Box 280)
  - Foreign Relations: Panama, 1978 February 7-March 9; (7 folders) (Box Box 281)
  - Foreign Relations: Panama, 1978 January-February 6, 1979-1982; (7 folders) (Box Box 282)
  - Foreign Relations: Panama - Special Lists, 1977-1978 (Box Box 283)
  - Foreign Relations: Philippines, 1973-1977 (Box Box 283)
  - Foreign Relations: Poland, 1981-1982 (Box Box 283)
  - Foreign Relations: Rhodesia, 1973-1976 June-December; (3 folders) (Box Box 283)
  - Foreign Relations: Rhodesia, 1976 February-May, 1977, 1978 October-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 284)
  - Foreign Relations: Rhodesia, 1978 January-September, 1979-1981; (6 folders) (Box Box 285)
  - Foreign Relations: Russia, 1973-1974; (3 folders) (Box Box 285)
  - Foreign Relations: Russia, 1975-1978; (6 folders) (Box Box 286)
  - Foreign Relations: Russia, 1979-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 287)
  - Foreign Relations: Russia - Shadrin, B.E., 1978 (Box Box 287)
  - Foreign Relations: Saudi Arabia, 1981 October-December; (2 folders) (Box Box 287)
  - Foreign Relations: Saudi Arabia, 1981 March-September; (5 folders) (Box Box 288)
  - Foreign Relations: State Department, 1974-1982 (Box Box 288)
  - Foreign Relations: State, Secretary of (Henry Kissinger), 1973 (Box Box 288)
  - Foreign Relations: State, Secretary of - Henry Kissinger, 1974-1977; (3 folders) (Box Box 289)
  - Foreign Relations: State, Secretary of, 1979-1982 (Box Box 289)
  - Foreign Relations: Treaties, 1973-1974; (4 folders) (Box Box 289)
  - Foreign Relations: Treaties, 1975-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 290)
  - Foreign Relations: Turkey, 1974-1977; (3 folders) (Box Box 290)
  - Foreign Relations: Turkey, 1978-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 291)
  - Foreign Relations: Venezuela Trip, 1974 (Box Box 291)
  - Foreign Relations: Vietnam, 1973 March 7-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 291)
  - Foreign Relations: Vietnam, 1973 January-March 1-6; (8 folders) (Box Box 292)
  - Foreign Relations: Vietnam, 1974-1975 April-November; (7 folders) (Box Box 293)
  - Foreign Relations: Vietnam, 1975 January-March, 1976-1982; (6 folders) (Box Box 294)
  - Foreign Relations: Vietnam - Aid to Children, 1974-1975 (Box Box 294)
  - Foreign Relations: Vietnam - Debate & Vote on Byrd Amendment re Aid, 1973 (Box Box 294)
  - Foreign Relations: Vietnam - M.I.A.'s & P.O.W.'s, 1973-1982; (6 folders) (Box Box 295)
  - Foreign Relations: Vietnam - P.O.W.'s Homecoming Information, 1973 (Box Box 295)
  - Foreign Relations: Zambia, 1972-1973 (Box Box 295)
  - Health, 1973-1974; (6 folders) (Box Box 296)
  - Health, 1975; (8 folders) (Box Box 297)
  - Health, 1976, 1977 November-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 298)
  - Health, 1977 January-October, 1978; (9 folders) (Box Box 299)
  - Health, 1979, 1980 October-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 300)
  - Health, 1980 January-September, 1981 August-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 301)
  - Health, 1981 January-July, 1982; (7 folders) (Box Box 302)
  - Health: Abortion, 1973 February 14-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 303)
  - Health: Abortion, 1973 January-February 13, 1974 March-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 304)
  - Health: Abortion, 1974 January-February, 1975 May-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 300)
  - Health: Abortion, 1975 January-April, 1976 April-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 306)
  - Health: Abortion, 1976 January-March, 1977 April-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 307)
  - Health: Abortion, 1977 January-March, 1978-79 May-December; (9 folders) (Box Box 308)
  - Health: Abortion, 1979 January-April, 1980-82 September-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 309)
  - Health: Abortion, 1982 January-August; (5 folders) (Box Box 310)
  - Health: Cancer, 1973-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 310)
  - Health: Disease, 1973-1981; (5 folders) (Box Box 311)
  - Health: Drugs, 1973; (4 folders) (Box Box 311)
  - Health: Drugs, 1974-1978; (9 folders) (Box Box 312)
  - Health: Drugs, 1979-1982 (Box Box 313)
  - Health: Emergency Medical Services Systems Act of 1973 (S. 504) (Box Box 313)
  - Health: Hospitals, 1973-1976; (7 folders) (Box Box 313)
  - Health: Hospitals, 1977-1982; (6 folders) (Box Box 314)
  - Health: Malpractice, 1976-1977 (Box Box 314)
  - Health: Medical Manpower & Training, 1973; (3 folders) (Box Box 314)
  - Health: Medical Manpower & Training, 1974-1978; (9 folders) (Box Box 315)
  - Health: Medical Manpower & Training, 1979-1981; (3 folders) (Box Box 316)
  - Health: Mental Health, 1973-1982; (3 folders) (Box Box 316)
  - Health: Public Health Service Act Extension of 1973 (S. 1136) (Box Box 316)
  - Health: Regional Medical Programs, 1973-1974 (Box Box 316)
  - Health: Research, 1973-1978 (Box Box 316)
  - Health: Youth Camp Safety, 1976-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 316)
  - Highways, 1973-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 317)
  - Highways: Billboards, 1973-1979 (Box Box 317)
  - Highways: Federal Aid Construction, 1973-1978 (Box Box 317)
  - Highways: Great Lakes to Florida Highway Association Incorporated - Williams, J.A., 1973-1979 (Box Box 317)
  - Highways: Highway Trust Fund, 1973 February-October, 1974-1977; (3 folders) (Box Box 318)
  - Highways: Speed Limits, 1974-1979 (Box Box 318)
  - Highways: Traffic Safety, 1973-1979; (3 folders) (Box Box 318)
  - Highways: Trucks, 1974 (Box Box 318)
  - Highways: Trucks, 1975-1979; (3 folders) (Box Box 319)
  - Housing, 1973-1974 October 9-December; (4 folders) (Box Box 319)
  - Housing, 1974 January-October 8, 1975 August-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 320)
  - Housing, 1975 January-July, 1976 October-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 321)
  - Housing, 1976 January-September, 1977 October-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 322)
  - Housing, 1977 January-September, 1978-1979, 1980 September-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 323)
  - Housing, 1980 January-July, 1981-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 324)
  - Housing: Fair Housing, 1974-1976 (Box Box 324)
  - Housing: Federal Housing Administration, 1973-1979 (Box Box 324)
  - Housing: Grants, 1977 & 1982 (Box Box 324)
  - Housing: Impounded Funds, 1973 (Box Box 324)
  - Housing: Interstate Land Sales, 1976 (Box Box 324)
  - Housing: Low Income, 1973 (Box Box 324)
  - Housing: Low Income, 1974-1979 (Box Box 325)
  - Housing: Manor Arms Apartment Complex, 1974 (Box Box 325)
  - Housing: Settlement Fees, 1973-1981 (Box Box 325)
  - Housing: Urban Renewal, 1973-1978; (4 folders) (Box Box 325)
  - Housing: Urban Renewal (Special Group), 1975 (Box Box 325)
  - Immigration, 1973-1978; (8 folders) (Box Box 326)
  - Immigration, 1979-1982; (7 folders) (Box Box 327)
  - Immigration: Lee, Robert E. [Robert E. Lee] - Citizenship, 1973-1975; (7 folders) (Box Box 328)
  - Immigration: Lee, Robert E. - Citizenship, 1976-1978 (Box Box 329)
  - Immigration: Naturalized Citizens, 1973-1974 (Box Box 329)
  - Immigration: Refugees, 1973-1980 (Box Box 329)
  - Immigration: Richmond Office Move, 1975-1976; (2 folders) (Box Box 329)
  - Immigration: Vietnamese, 1975; (2 folders) (Box Box 329)
  - Industry, 1972-1981; (6 folders) (Box Box 330)
  - Industry: Antitrust, 1973-1975, 1976 May-November; (3 folders) (Box Box 330)
  - Industry: Antitrust, 1976 January-April, 1977-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 331)
  - Industry: Automobiles, 1973-1974; (2 folders) (Box Box 331)
  - Industry: Automobiles, 1975-1979; (9 folders) (Box Box 332)
  - Industry: Automobiles, 1980-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 333)
  - Industry: FDA - Drugs, 1973, 1974 August-December; (5 folders) (Box Box 333)
  - Industry: FDA - Drugs, 1974 January-July, 1975-1982; (7 folders) (Box Box 334)
  - Industry: FDA - Food, 1974 & 1979 (Box Box 334)
  - Industry: Fishing 200 Mile Limit, 1974-1979; (3 folders) (Box Box 335)
  - Industry: Franchises, 1973-1979 (Box Box 335)
  - Industry: Lumber, 1973-1974 (Box Box 335)
  - Industry: Petroleum, 1974-1976; (4 folders) (Box Box 335)
  - Industry: Regulation of Shellfish, 1975 (Box Box 336)
  - Industry: Steel, 1974-1978; (3 folders) (Box Box 336)
  - Industry: Toxic Substances, 1973-1978; (3 folders) (Box Box 336)
  - Industry: Tourism, 1974-1980 (Box Box 336)
  - Insurance, 1973-1982; (6 folders) (Box Box 337)
  - Insurance: Auto - No-Fault, 1973 May-December; (3 folders) (Box Box 337)
  - Insurance: Auto - No-Fault, 1973 January-April, 1974 March-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 338)
  - Insurance: Auto - No-Fault, 1974 January-February, 1975-1981; (7 folders) (Box Box 339)
  - Insurance: Auto - No-Fault (S. 354), 1972-1974 (Box Box 339)
  - Insurance: Auto - No-Fault (S. 945), 1972 (Box Box 340)
  - Insurance: Blue Cross - Blue Shield, 1975-1982 (Box Box 340)
  - Insurance: Crop, 1978-1980 (Box Box 340)
  - Insurance: Flood, 1974-1979; (3 folders) (Box Box 340)
  - Insurance: Health, 1973, 1974 June-December; (3 folders) (Box Box 340)
  - Insurance: Health, 1974 January-May, 1975-1979; (9 folders) (Box Box 341)
  - Insurance: Health, 1980-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 342)
  - Insurance: Life, 1973-1982 (Box Box 342)
  - Insurance: Private Pension Plans, 1973 October 8-December; (5 folders) (Box Box 342)
  - Insurance: Private Pension Plans, 1973 August-October 5; (8 folders) (Box Box 343)
  - Insurance: Private Pension Plans, 1973 January-July, 1974-1979; (7 folders) (Box Box 344)
  - Insurance: Unemployment, 1975-1977 (Box Box 344)
  - Labor, 1974-1980; (8 folders) (Box Box 345)
  - Labor, 1981-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 346)
  - Labor: Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA), 1977 (Box Box 346)
  - Labor: CETA, 1978-1981; (3 folders) (Box Box 347)
  - Labor: Coal Mine Health & Safety, 1973-1980 (Box Box 347)
  - Labor: Davis-Bacon Wage Rater Determinations, 1973-1981; (3 folders) (Box Box 347)
  - Labor: Disputes, 1973-1974 (Box Box 347)
  - Labor: Disputes, 1975-1978 (Box Box 348)
  - Labor: Employment, 1973-1975; (6 folders) (Box Box 348)
  - Labor: Employment, 1976, 1977 May-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 349)
  - Labor: Employment, 1977 January-April, 1978-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 350)
  - Labor: Equal Employment Opportunities, 1973-1981; (2 folders) (Box Box 350)
  - Labor: Fair Labor Standards, 1974-1977 (Box Box 350)
  - Labor: Manpower Development & Training, 1973-1977; (4 folders) (Box Box 351)
  - Labor: Minimum Wage, 1973 July-November; (2 folders) (Box Box 351)
  - Labor: Minimum Wage, 1973 February-May, 1974-1976, 1977 August-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 352)
  - Labor: Minimum Wage, 1977 January-July, 1978-1981; (7 folders) (Box Box 353)
  - Labor: National Labor Relations Board, 1974-1975 (Box Box 353)
  - Labor: National Labor Relations Board, 1976-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 354)
  - Labor: Occupational Health & Safety, 1972-1980; (3 folders) (Box Box 354)
  - Labor: Occupational Safety - Organophosphorous Pesticides, 1973; (5 folders) (Box Box 355)
  - Labor: OSHA, 1973-1974; (2 folders) (Box Box 355)
  - Labor: OSHA, 1975-1981; (7 folders) (Box Box 356)
  - Labor: Railroad Retirement, 1973 June-December; (2 folders) (Box Box 356)
  - Labor: Railroad Retirement, 1973 February-May, 1974; (6 folders) (Box Box 357)
  - Labor: Railroad Retirement, 1975-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 358)
  - Labor: Railroad Retirement (H.R. 7200), 1973 (Box Box 358)
  - Labor: Strikes, 1973-1981; (2 folders) (Box Box 358)
  - Labor: Taft-Hartley, 1973-1974, 1975 November-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 359)
  - Labor: Taft-Hartley, 1975 August-October; (6 folders) (Box Box 360)
  - Labor: Taft-Hartley, 1975 January-July, 1976, 1977 April-November; (9 folders) (Box Box 361)
  - Labor: Taft-Hartley, 1977 January-March; (2 folders) (Box Box 362)
  - Labor: Unemployment Compensation, 1973-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 362)
  - Labor: Unions, 1973 (Box Box 362)
  - Labor: Unions, 1974-1976; (7 folders) (Box Box 363)
  - Labor: Unions, 1977; (7 folders) (Box Box 364)
  - Labor: Unions, 1978 March-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 365)
  - Labor: Unions, 1978 January-February; (4 folders) (Box Box 366)
  - Labor: Unions - Form Letter Response, 1978; (3 folders) (Box Box 366)
  - Labor: Unions, 1979-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 367)
  - Labor: Workmen's Compensation, 1973-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 367)
  - Natural Resources, 1973-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 368)
  - Natural Resources: Coal Mining, 1972-1973; (3 folders) (Box Box 368)
  - Natural Resources: Coal Mining, 1974-1975, 1976 July-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 369)
  - Natural Resources: Coal Mining, 1976 January-June, 1977-1982; (6 folders) (Box Box 370)
  - Natural Resources: Coal Mining - Surface Mining (H.R. 6482 & S. 630), 1972-1973, n.d. (Box Box 370)
  - Natural Resources: Fish & Wildlife, 1973-1974; (9 folders) (Box Box 371)
  - Natural Resources: Fish & Wildlife, 1975, 1976 July-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 372)
  - Natural Resources: Fish & Wildlife, 1976 January-June, 1977; (9 folders) (Box Box 373)
  - Natural Resources: Fish & Wildlife, 1978, 1979 June-December; (9 folders) (Box Box 374)
  - Natural Resources: Fish & Wildlife, 1979 January-May, 1980-1982; (8 folders) (Box Box 375)
  - Natural Resources: Flood Control, 1973-1978 (Box Box 375)
  - Natural Resources: Forestry, 1973-1976; (8 folders) (Box Box 376)
  - Natural Resources: Forestry, 1977-1981; (4 folders) (Box Box 377)
  - Natural Resources: Gas, 1973-1977; (5 folders) (Box Box 377)
  - Natural Resources: Gas, 1978-1981 (Box Box 378)
  - Natural Resources: Land Use, 1973-1981; (5 folders) (Box Box 378)
  - Natural Resources: National Parks, 1973-1976; (2 folders) (Box Box 378)
  - Natural Resources: National Parks, 1977-1982; (7 folders) (Box Box 379)
  - Natural Resources: Oil/Petroleum, 1973-1979; (7 folders) (Box Box 380)
  - Natural Resources: Rivers & Harbors, 1973-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 381)
  - Natural Resources: Wilderness, 1973; (6 folders) (Box Box 381)
  - Natural Resources: Wilderness, 1974-1978; (7 folders) (Box Box 382)
  - Natural Resources: Wilderness, 1979-1982; (7 folders) (Box Box 383)
  - Political Affairs, 1973-1975 (Box Box 383)
  - Political Affairs, 1976-1982; (7 folders) (Box Box 384)
  - Political Affairs: Byrd for Senate '82 - For, 1982; (3 folders) (Box Box 385)
  - Political Affairs: Byrd for Senate '82 - Against, 1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 385)
  - Political Affairs: Campaign Financing & Contributions, 1970, 1973 August-December; (2 folders) (Box Box 385)
  - Political Affairs: Campaign Financing & Contributions, 1973 January-July, 1974-1978; (7 folders) (Box Box 386)
  - Political Affairs: Campaign Financing & Contributions, 1979-1982 (Box Box 387)
  - Political Affairs: Campaign Reforms, 1977; (2 folders) (Box Box 387)
  - Political Affairs: Democratic Senate Campaign Committee, 1974-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 387)
  - Political Affairs: Electoral College, 1973-1981 (Box Box 387)
  - Political Affairs: Lobbying, 1975-1978 (Box Box 387)
  - Political Affairs: National Elections & Campaigns, 1973-1982; (8 folders) (Box Box 388)
  - Political Affairs: New Hampshire Senate Race, 1975 (Box Box 388)
  - Political Affairs: Politicians - Thomas Thomson Byrd, 1973 (Box Box 388)
  - Political Affairs: Politicians - Candidates for Office, 1973-1974 (Box Box 389)
  - Political Affairs: Politicians - J. Carter, 1976 (Box Box 389)
  - Political Affairs: Politicians - Marshall Coleman, 1981 (Box Box 389)
  - Political Affairs: Politicians - D. E. Earman (former Gov.), 1973 (Box Box 389)
  - Political Affairs: Politicians - J. T. Fitzpatrick, 1973 (Box Box 389)
  - Political Affairs: Politicians - Mills Godwin, Governor, 1973; (3 folders) (Box Box 389)
  - Political Affairs: Politicians - Linwood Holton, Governor, 1973 (Box Box 389)
  - Political Affairs: Politicians - Henry E. Howell, Jr., 1969-1973 (Box Box 389)
  - Political Affairs: Politicians - Edward E. Lane, Lieutenant Governor, 1973 (Box Box 389)
  - Political Affairs: Politicians - P. S. McDonnell, 1973 (Box Box 389)
  - Political Affairs: Politicians - Francis Pickens Miller, 1977 (Box Box 389)
  - Political Affairs: Politicians - Daniel Patrick Moynihan, 1975 (Box Box 389)
  - Political Affairs: Politicians - Richard D. Obenshain, 1973 (Box Box 389)
  - Political Affairs: Politicians - Ronald Reagan, 1973 (Box Box 389)
  - Political Affairs: Politicians - Charles S. Robb, 1981 (Box Box 389)
  - Political Affairs: Politicians - William L. Scott, 1973 (Box Box 389)
  - Political Affairs: Politicians - William B. Spong, 1973 (Box Box 389)
  - Political Affairs: Politicians - Paul S. Trible, 1982 (Box Box 389)
  - Political Affairs: Politicians - Elmo Zumwalt, 1975-1977; (2 folders) (Box Box 389)
  - Political Affairs: Presidential, 1973-1981; (3 folders) (Box Box 390)
  - Political Affairs: Republican Senate Campaign Committee, 1974-1981 (Box Box 390)
  - Political Affairs: Virginia Elections & Campaigns, 1973-1977; (5 folders) (Box Box 390)
  - Political Affairs: Virginia Elections & Campaigns, 1978-1982; (8 folders) (Box Box 391)
  - Political Affairs: Voter Registration, 1975-1982; (3 folders) (Box Box 392)
  - Political Affairs: Voting Record, 1973-1981 (Box Box 392)
  - Pollution, 1973-1981 (Box Box 392)
  - Pollution: Air, 1973 June-December; (2 folders) (Box Box 392)
  - Pollution: Air, 1973 January-May, 1974-1975, 1976 May-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 393)
  - Pollution: Air, 1976 January-April, 1977-1979; (7 folders) (Box Box 394)
  - Pollution: Air, 1980-1982 (Box Box 395)
  - Pollution: Environmental Protection Agency, 1973-1979 (Box Box 395)
  - Pollution: Grants, 1977-1982 (Box Box 395)
  - Pollution: Noise, 1973-1981 (Box Box 395)
  - Pollution: Pesticides, 1972-1977 (Box Box 395)
  - Pollution: Solid Waste, 1973-1975; (3 folders) (Box Box 395)
  - Pollution: Solid Waste, 1976-1981; (3 folders) (Box Box 396)
  - Pollution: Water, 1973-1976; (5 folders) (Box Box 396)
  - Pollution: Water, 1977-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 397)
  - Pornography, 1973-1977; (3 folders) (Box Box 397)
  - Pornography, 1978-1981 (Box Box 398)
  - Postal Service, 1973-1982 (Box Box 398)
  - Postal Service: Legislation, 1973-1976; (4 folders) (Box Box 398)
  - Postal Service: Legislation, 1977-1982; (6 folders) (Box Box 399)
  - Postal Service: Operations, 1978-1981 (Box Box 399)
  - Postal Service: Rates, 1973-1982; (3 folders) (Box Box 400)
  - Postal Service: Stamp Suggestions, 1973-1977; (2 folders) (Box Box 400)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments, 1971-1972 (Box Box 400)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 7 - Albemarle County, 1965-1970 (Box Box 401)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 7 - Augusta County, 1966-1969 (Box Box 401)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 7 - Bath, Clark, Culpeper & Frederick Counties, 1965-1972 (Box Box 401)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 7 - Charlottesville, 1968-1971 (Box Box 401)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 7 - Harrisonburg, 1970-1972 (Box Box 401)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 7 - Lexington, 1968 (Box Box 401)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 7 - Madison, Orange, & Page Counties, 1967-1972 (Box Box 401)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 7 - Rappahannock, Rockbridge, & Rockingham Counties, 1963-1970 (Box Box 401)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 7 - Shenandoah & Warren Counties, 1958-1972 (Box Box 401)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 7 - Staunton, 1970 (Box Box 401)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 7 - Winchester, 1966-1968 (Box Box 401)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 8 - Caroline, Charles City, Essex, & Fairfax Counties, 1966-1969 (Box Box 402)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 8 - Fauquier & Goochland Counties, 1967-1972 (Box Box 402)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 8 - Fredericksburg, 1966-1969 (Box Box 402)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 8 - Hanover County, 1959-1972 (Box Box 402)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 8 - Henrico, Highland, King & Queen, & King George County, 1966-1971 (Box Box 402)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 8 - King William & Lancaster Counties, 1967-1972 (Box Box 402)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 8 - Loudon County, 1967-1970 (Box Box 402)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 8 - Louisa & New Kent Counties, 1967-1969 (Box Box 403)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 8 - Northumberland, Powhatan, Prince Edward, & Prince George Counties, 1966-1972 (Box Box 403)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 8 - Prince William County, 1968-1972 (Box Box 403)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 8 - Richmond, Spotsylvania, & Stafford Counties, 1966-1969 (Box Box 403)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 8 - Westmoreland County, 1966-1969 (Box Box 403)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 9 - Bland, Buchanan, & Dickerson Counties, 1958-1970 (Box Box 403)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 9 - Bristol & Norton Counties, 1967-1969 (Box Box 403)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 9 - Giles County, 1967-1969 (Box Box 403)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 9 - Lee & Pulaski Counties, 1966-1972 (Box Box 403)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 9 - Russell & Scott Counties, 1967-1969 (Box Box 404)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 9 - Smyth County, 1967-1972 (Box Box 404)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 9 - Tazewell County, 1966-1972 (Box Box 404)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 9 - Washington & Wythe Counties, 1961-1972 (Box Box 404)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 9 - Wise County, 1958-1969 (Box Box 404)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 10 - Alexandria, Annandale, Falls Church, & Fairfax City, 1967-1971 (Box Box 404)
  - Postal Service: Postmaster Appointments: District 10 - Arlington & Fairfax Counties, 1967-1971 (Box Box 404)
  - President, 1974-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 405)
  - President: Communications From, 1973-1975; (5 folders) (Box Box 405)
  - President: Communications From, 1976-1977, 1978 July-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 406)
  - President: Communications From, 1978 January-June, 1979-1982; (6 folders) (Box Box 407)
  - President: Communications From (Special Folder), 1971-1982 (Box Box 408)
  - President: Communications To, 1973-1982 (Box Box 408)